Satoshi, who aims to battle
the Supreme Monarch, Dande...
＜最強の王者
ﾀﾞﾝﾃﾞとのﾊﾞﾄﾙを目指すｻﾄｼ｡
And Go, who dreams of catching every Pokémon
to work his way up to Mew...
すべてのﾎﾟｹﾓﾝをｹﾞｯﾄし[外:583134B86E7D90960F64C5B863196978]
ﾐｭｳにたどり着くという
夢を持つ ｺﾞｳ｡
This is the story of their lives and adventures.
これは そんな２人の日常と
冒険を描く物語である＞
(ﾗﾋﾞﾌｯﾄ)ﾋﾞﾌﾋﾞﾌ｡
(ﾋﾟｶﾁｭｳ)ﾋﾟｶﾋﾟｶ！
Satoshi continues to fight in
the Pokémon World Championships,
＜ﾎﾟｹﾓﾝ･ﾜｰﾙﾄﾞ･ﾁｬﾝﾋﾟｵﾝｼｯﾌﾟｽに
挑戦を続けるｻﾄｼは 現在890位｡
and is currently ranked 890th.
So far, he’s maintained
a flawless winning streak.
このところ連戦連勝｡
Yamabuki City, Kanto Region
次なる対戦者を求めて
やってきたのは ﾔﾏﾌﾞｷｼﾃｨだ＞
Seeking his next challenge,
he’s come to Yamabuki City.
うん いい動きだ｡
(ｻﾄｼ)でしょ！
Yes. Its moves are sharp.
Aren’t they?
I feel like we’re totally unstoppable!
俺たち今 全然負ける気が
しないっていうか｡
ﾋﾟｶﾁｭｰ｡
この格闘道場で[外:583134B86E7D90960F64C5B863196978]
Are you sure you should
be boasting so much in the Fighting Dojo?
そんな大口たたいていいのかな？
うちの空手大王は
一筋縄じゃいかないぞ｡
Our Karate Master is no trifling foe.
Think he’ll battle me?
ﾊﾞﾄﾙ やってもらえますか？
今 ﾊﾞﾄﾙ中だ｡
He’s battling
someone else right now.
A challenger arrived
before you.
さっき挑戦者がやってきてね｡
ええっ!?
Huh?
な～に すぐ終わるよ｡
大王が負けるわけないさ｡
Worry not.
He’ll be done shortly.
The Master cannot lose!
(掛け声)
Hey, Go, let’s watch the battle!
おい ｺﾞｳ｡ ﾊﾞﾄﾙ見に行こうぜ！
ﾋﾟｰｶ！
まだ迷ってるようだね｡
It seems you’re still unsure.
(ｺﾞｳ)う～ん｡
Go!
ｺﾞｳ！
あっ ｻﾄｼ｡
Oh, Satoshi.
You can’t pick between
Ebiwarar and Sawamurar?
ｴﾋﾞﾜﾗｰとｻﾜﾑﾗｰ
どっちか決めらんないのか？
う～ん 鋭いﾊﾟﾝﾁの連打
ｴﾋﾞﾜﾗｰにするか[外:583134B86E7D90960F64C5B863196978]
Should I go with Ebiwarar
and his barrage of focused punches,
破壊力抜群のｷｯｸ ｻﾜﾑﾗｰにするか｡
or Sawamurar with his
immensely destructive kicks?
Do I really have to pick just one?
どうしても どっちか１つに
決めなきゃだめですか？
Indeed. That’s the rule.
ああ それが決まりだ｡
The Fighting Dojo
can only give trainers...
格闘道場からﾄﾚｰﾅｰに
あげることができるのは[外:583134B86E7D90960F64C5B863196978]
ｻﾜﾑﾗｰかｴﾋﾞﾜﾗｰ
どちらか１体だけさ｡
...Sawamurar or Ebiwarar.
One or the other.
Satoshi, I know!
We’ll get one each!
そうだ ｻﾄｼ
お前と俺で１体ずつもらおう｡
Then you can trade for mine!
それで 俺のﾎﾟｹﾓﾝと交換しよう｡
え～っ!?
Huh?!
A Championships Trainer is nearby.
(ｽﾏﾎﾛﾄﾑ)ﾁｬﾝﾋﾟｵﾝｼｯﾌﾟｽのﾄﾚｰﾅｰが
近くにいます｡
ﾋﾟｶ！
ということは[外:583134B86E7D90960F64C5B863196978]
That must mean...
今来てる挑戦者だな｡
そうか！
...the challenger battling right now.
I see!
ＰＯＣＫＥＴＭｏＮＳｔｅＲｓ
PocketMonsters
Hey, you still not ready? C'mon, hurry up!
You all packed and ready to leave?
I'll show you this wide mysterious world
And skip the slow send-off
Be it through fire or through water
I'm fumbling blindly through the days
When I don't even know what the next second will bring
Each and every one of my memories
Can always be found inside a Ball
On 1, 2, 3, dive in!
I've got the future plans I imagined in my pocket
Greeting someone new is always fresh
No need to hesitate! Try!
Let's have a fight!
1: Once the battle's done
2: And we're laughing or crying
On 3, let's be friends!
Any day and every day, that's always been my rule
With this unpredictable, boundless world awaiting
Let's go! Every time you trip and fall
Let's go! You pick yourself up by my side
I choose you!
The Terror of Otosupus!!
Saito, the Lone Warrior!
Let’s go, everyone!
みんな 行くぞ！
ﾋﾟｶ！
(ﾘｵﾙ)ﾘｵ！
たのも…｡
Excuse—
ﾋﾟｶ！
うわ…｡
Satoshi, are you okay?!
大丈夫か？ ｻﾄｼ｡
Ebiwarar?!
ｴﾋﾞﾜﾗｰ？
(ﾗﾋﾞﾌｯﾄ)ﾋﾞﾌｯ！
(空手大王)ｸｯ…｡
(ﾒｯｿﾝ)ﾒｿ…｡
(空手大王)
ｸﾞﾇﾇ… ここまでであったか｡
I did not anticipate
such power...
(ｻｲﾄｳ)審判 結審を｡
Referee, call it.
O-Of course!
は… はい！ ｵﾄｽﾊﾟｽの勝ち｡
Otosupus wins!
As such, the winner is Saito!
よって 勝者 ｻｲﾄｳ！
Are you okay, Ebiwarar?
大丈夫か？ ｴﾋﾞﾜﾗｰ｡
ﾘｵ｡
ﾋﾟｶ｡
Ebiwarar!
ｴﾋﾞﾜﾗｰ｡
(ｴﾋﾞﾜﾗｰ)ｴﾋﾞ｡
よく戦ったな ｴﾋﾞﾜﾗｰ｡
戻ってくれ｡
You fought well, Ebiwarar.
Return.
我らが空手大王が
手も足も出なかったとは｡
I can’t believe it...
Our Karate Master was utterly helpless.
Otosupus is formidable.
恐るべきは ｵﾄｽﾊﾟｽ｡ ﾄﾚｰﾅｰもまた[外:583134B86E7D90960F64C5B863196978]
Its trainer demonstrated an
utterly impeccable fighting technique, too.
一分の隙なき完璧な戦いだった｡
ｵﾄｽﾊﾟｽ？
ﾘｵ？
ﾋﾟｶ｡
Otosupus?
Return, Otosupus.
戻れ ｵﾄｽﾊﾟｽ｡
That was a fine battle.
I thank you.
よきﾊﾞﾄﾙでした｡ 感謝します｡
[外:7542BC0875D546542D2435DAA99821BB]
That’s for the Championships?
それは ﾁｬﾝﾋﾟｵﾝｼｯﾌﾟｽの｡
(ｽﾏﾎﾛﾄﾑ)公式ﾊﾞﾄﾙのご案内です｡
This is an official
battle announcement.
ﾁｬﾝﾋﾟｵﾝｼｯﾌﾟｽにｴﾝﾄﾘｰしてる
ﾄﾚｰﾅｰですね｡
You’re signed up for the Championships?
(ｽﾏﾎﾛﾄﾑ)
ﾊﾞﾄﾙしますか？ しませんか？
Would you like to battle? Or not?
My name is Satoshi.
俺 ｻﾄｼっていいます｡
I’m fighting in the Championships, too.
I’d like to battle you!
俺もﾁｬﾝﾋﾟｵﾝｼｯﾌﾟｽに挑戦中なんです｡
ﾊﾞﾄﾙをお願いします｡
I accept your challenge.
挑戦を受けましょう｡
ﾎﾝﾄ？ やった！
Really? All right!
ﾋﾟｶ！
ﾘｵ！
Official battle appointment made!
(ｽﾏﾎﾛﾄﾑ)公式ﾊﾞﾄﾙ 成立です｡
My name is Saito.
I hail from Galar.
私は ｻｲﾄｳ｡ ｶﾞﾗﾙから来ました｡
Galar?
ｶﾞﾗﾙ!?
May we use this arena?
ここを使ってもいいですか？
おお かまいませんとも｡
By all means.
ｻﾄｼくんと言ったな｡
You said your name was Satoshi, yes?
I am the owner of this Fighting Dojo.
They call me the Karate Master.
わしはここ 格闘道場の主
人呼んで 空手大王だ｡
You may use this place as you see fit.
この場を
存分に使ってくれていいぞ｡
Thank you, Karate Master!
ありがとうございます 空手大王｡
君もﾊﾞﾄﾙを？
Are you here to battle, too?
Oh, no, I heard I could get
Ebiwarar or Sawamurar if I came here.
あっ 俺は ここに来ると
ｴﾋﾞﾜﾗｰとｻﾜﾑﾗｰ[外:583134B86E7D90960F64C5B863196978]
どっちかもらえると聞いて｡
ｳﾑ 確かにな｡
Indeed you can.
That is, if you can defeat me in battle.
しかし それは
わしとのﾊﾞﾄﾙに勝ったらの話だ｡
I have to battle?!
ﾊﾞﾄﾙするんですか！
Well, first let us observe
Lady Saito’s battle.
まぁ まずはｻｲﾄｳ殿のﾊﾞﾄﾙを
見学するとよいだろう｡
ﾎﾟｹﾓﾝと共に生き
ﾎﾟｹﾓﾝとともに戦う者｡
Live alongside Pokémon...
Battle alongside Pokémon...
その１つの答えが ここにある｡
One way to do that lies here.
Lady Saito is a Gym Leader
in the Galar Region, you see.
(空手大王)
ｻｲﾄｳ殿は ｶﾞﾗﾙ地方のｼﾞﾑﾘｰﾀﾞｰでな｡
ｼﾞﾑﾘｰﾀﾞｰ!?
A Gym Leader?!
She is known as both
the Fighting-type Gym Leader...
格闘ﾀｲﾌﾟのｼﾞﾑﾘｰﾀﾞｰを務める一方…｡
ﾊｯ！
...and as a master of
the century-old art of Galar Karate.
(空手大王)
100年の歴史を持つｶﾞﾗﾙ空手の[外:583134B86E7D90960F64C5B863196978]
達人としても知られている｡
Furthermore, she travels around
visiting dojos all over the world,
更にはこうして
世界各地の道場を訪ね歩き[外:583134B86E7D90960F64C5B863196978]
battling, refining both herself
and her Pokémon,
ﾊﾞﾄﾙを行って
ﾎﾟｹﾓﾝと我が身を鍛え[外:583134B86E7D90960F64C5B863196978]
in pursuit of even greater strength.
より高みを目指さんと
しておられる｡
Her rank is higher than yours.
ｻﾄｼより順位は上だ｡
751st, huh?
今 751位か｡
I’m in the Super Class, too.
I’m 890th.
俺も ｽｰﾊﾟｰｸﾗｽです｡ 890位｡
We’ve won every match
we’ve had so far!
ここまで俺たち 連戦連勝｡
Riolu here has worked
particularly hard!
特に このﾘｵﾙが
頑張ってくれてるんです｡
ﾘｵ！
ﾋﾟｶﾁｭｰ！
確かに たぎる気合いを感じる｡
よく育てられているようだ｡
I can indeed feel a burning fighting spirit from it.
It seems to have been trained well.
I knew you’d be able to tell,
Karate Master!
わかります？ さすが 空手大王！
Hey! I don’t think
you should be so cocky!
おい あんまり調子に
のらないほうが[外:583134B86E7D90960F64C5B863196978]
いいんじゃないのか！
相手は相当に格上だぞ！
Your opponent is ranked
far above you!
心配すんなって｡
格闘ﾀｲﾌﾟのｼﾞﾑﾘｰﾀﾞｰなら[外:583134B86E7D90960F64C5B863196978]
Don’t worry!
Speaking of Fighting-type Gym Leaders,
この前 ｺﾙﾆに勝っただろ｡
I beat Corni the other day, remember?
Corni?
ｺﾙﾆ…｡
ｺﾙﾆを知ってるんですか？
You know her?
I have battled her.
以前 勝負しました｡
Her skills were inadequate.
甘いですね 彼女は｡
どういうことですか｡
ﾘｵ？
ﾋﾟｶ？
What’s that supposed to mean?
There is no need
for me to say more.
他に語る必要はありません｡
Why did you sign up?
なぜ ｴﾝﾄﾘｰを？
Because I wanna get stronger
with my Pokémon!
ﾎﾟｹﾓﾝと一緒に強くなりたいから｡
And if I keep climbing the ranks,
I’ll be able to battle Mr. Dande!
この調子で順位を上げていけば
ﾀﾞﾝﾃﾞさんとﾊﾞﾄﾙができる｡
Mr. Dande, is it?
ﾀﾞﾝﾃﾞさん… ですか｡
ﾀﾞﾝﾃﾞさんは すべての
ﾄﾚｰﾅｰにとっての目標です｡
Mr. Dande is every trainer’s goal.
私は あの方を倒し
正真正銘の最強となりたい｡
I wish to defeat him and become
the undisputed strongest.
ゆえに ｴﾝﾄﾘｰしました｡
Thus I signed up
for the Championships.
I’ll be the strongest!
We will defeat Mr. Dande!
最強になるのは俺だ！
ﾀﾞﾝﾃﾞさんは俺たちが倒す！
Let us hold nothing back
in our battle!
存分に戦いましょう！
Don’t panic, Satoshi! Just do
as you always do, and you’ll win, for sure!
ｻﾄｼ 焦るな｡
お前らしくいけば きっと勝てる｡
Yeah, I got this!
ああ 任せとけって｡
Pikachu! Riolu!
Let’s do this!
ﾋﾟｶﾁｭｳ ﾘｵﾙ やるぞ！
ﾋﾟｶ！
ﾘｵ！
The Pokémon World Championships
has approved this Super Class battle!
(ﾄﾞﾛｰﾝﾛﾄﾑ)ﾎﾟｹﾓﾝ･ﾜｰﾙﾄﾞ･ﾁｬﾝﾋﾟｵﾝｼｯﾌﾟｽは
ｽｰﾊﾟｰｸﾗｽのﾊﾞﾄﾙを承認しました｡
The match-up is Contestant Saito
VS Contestant Satoshi.
対戦ｶｰﾄﾞ ｻｲﾄｳ選手 ﾊﾞｰｻｽ ｻﾄｼ選手｡
今回は ２対２で
ﾊﾞﾄﾙを行っていただきます｡
This battle will be a 2v2.
All right, both sides send out
your Pokémon at the same time.
では 両者同時に
ﾎﾟｹﾓﾝを出してください｡
ｽﾘｰ ﾂｰ ﾜﾝ ｺﾞｰ！
3! 2! 1! Go!
Luchabull, go forth!
ﾙﾁｬﾌﾞﾙ いっけ～！
いけ ｶﾓﾈｷﾞ！
You’re up, Kamonegi!
(ﾙﾁｬﾌﾞﾙ)ﾙﾁｬｰ！
(ｶﾓﾈｷﾞ)ｶｰﾓｯ！
Rotom, who’s that Pokémon?
ﾛﾄﾑ あのﾎﾟｹﾓﾝは？
Luchabull! Wrestling Pokémon!
Fighting/Flying type!
(ｽﾏﾎﾛﾄﾑ)ﾙﾁｬﾌﾞﾙ ﾚｽﾘﾝｸﾞﾎﾟｹﾓﾝ｡
かくとう･ひこうﾀｲﾌﾟ｡
With its wings,
it controls its position in the air!
翼を使い 空中で姿勢をｺﾝﾄﾛｰﾙ｡
すばやい技で相手を圧倒する｡
It overwhelms opponents with quick moves!
ﾙﾁｬﾌﾞﾙか｡
ｶﾓﾈｷﾞ 空中戦法に気をつけろ｡
Luchabull, huh? Kamonegi,
watch out for its air attacks!
ｷｬﾓ｡
Battle, start!
ﾊﾞﾄﾙ ｽﾀｰﾄ｡
Hone Claws!
つめとぎ！
ﾙﾁｬｰ！
Kamonegi,
use Crossroad Kill!
ｶﾓﾈｷﾞ つじぎりだ！
ｶﾓｶﾓｶﾓ！
ＰＯＣＫＥＴＭｏＮＳｔｅＲｓ
PocketMonsters
Pocket Monsters!
ＰＯＣＫＥＴＭｏＮＳｔｅＲｓ
PocketMonsters
Fighting
Riolu
ﾋﾟｶ！
ﾘｵ｡
ﾋﾟｶﾋﾟｶ！
ｶﾓｶﾓｶﾓ！
It’s got perfect balance!
ああっ！
なんてﾊﾞﾗﾝｽ｡
Karate Chop!
からてﾁｮｯﾌﾟ！
ｶﾓｰ！
Kamonegi!
ｶﾓﾈｷﾞ！
Flying Press!
ﾌﾗｲﾝｸﾞﾌﾟﾚｽ｡
Kamonegi, grab your leek!
ｶﾓﾈｷﾞ ﾈｷﾞを取れ！
ｶﾓ ｶﾓ！
よし！
All right!
Good, Kamonegi!
いいぞ ｶﾓﾈｷﾞ｡
ﾋﾞﾌ！
ﾁｬｰ｡
今だ｡ ぶんまわす攻撃！
Now! Brutal Swing!
ｶﾓｰ！
Spin it around!
どんどん回せ！
Finish it.
Flying Press!
決めます｡ ﾌﾗｲﾝｸﾞﾌﾟﾚｽ｡
ｶﾓ…｡
Look up!
上だ！
ｶﾓ？
ああっ！
Kamonegi is unable to battle!
ｶﾓﾈｷﾞ 戦闘不能｡
ﾋﾟｶ…｡
そんな…｡
No way...
Return, Kamonegi!
戻れ ｶﾓﾈｷﾞ｡
Kamonegi, you did great.
ｶﾓﾈｷﾞ よく戦ってくれた｡
ﾋﾟｰｶ｡
次は こうはいかない！
It won’t be so easy next time!
It seems she has complete
control over the battle.
彼は完全に相手に
のまれてしまっているようだな｡
戻した!?
She called it back?!
Otosupus, go forth!
ｵﾄｽﾊﾟｽ いっけ～！
(ｵﾄｽﾊﾟｽ)ｵｽﾊﾟｰ｡
Here it comes.
きたな｡
ﾋﾟｶ｡
Otosupus. Jujitsu Pokémon.
Fighting type.
(ｽﾏﾎﾛﾄﾑ)ｵﾄｽﾊﾟｽ 柔術ﾎﾟｹﾓﾝ｡
かくとうﾀｲﾌﾟ｡
A body made up of nothing but muscle...
全身が筋肉の塊｡
触手を使って繰り出す
絞め技の威力は すさまじい｡
...makes the grappling moves this Pokémon performs
with its tentacles tremendously powerful.
That was the Pokémon you were battling
when we came in, right?
俺たちが入ってきたときに
ﾊﾞﾄﾙしてたﾎﾟｹﾓﾝですよね｡
Yes.
ああ｡ わしのｻﾜﾑﾗｰもｴﾋﾞﾜﾗｰも[外:583134B86E7D90960F64C5B863196978]
Neither my Sawamurar nor my Ebiwarar
stood a chance against it.
まったく歯が立たなかった相手だ｡
ﾋﾟｶﾁｭｰ！ ﾋﾟ…｡
Riolu, you’ll go?
ﾘｵﾙ お前が行くのか？
All right!
Riolu, I choose you!
よし ﾘｵﾙ ｷﾐに決めた！
ﾘｵ！
Pikachu, cheer us on!
ﾋﾟｶﾁｭｳ 応援頼む！
ﾋﾟｶ｡
My second is Riolu!
俺の２体目は ﾘｵﾙだ｡
Battle, start!
ﾊﾞﾄﾙ ｽﾀｰﾄ｡
しんくうは！
Vacuum Wave!
ﾘｵ｡
Charge in!
Detect!
突っ込め みきり！
ｵｽﾊﾟｰ｡
ｲﾝﾌｧｲﾄ！
Infight!
Shadow Clones!
かげぶんしん！
ｱｸｱﾌﾞﾚｲｸ｡
Aqua Break!
Ward them off, Riolu!
ﾘｵﾙ 受け流すんだ！
ﾘｵ～！
That technique was what defeated
my Sawamurar and Ebiwarar.
わしのｻﾜﾑﾗｰも ｴﾋﾞﾜﾗｰも
あれでやられたんだ｡
Are you okay, Riolu?
大丈夫か ﾘｵﾙ｡
ﾋﾟｶ！
ﾘｵ！
I can’t predict its moves.
やつの動きが読めない｡
What do we do?
どうする？
ﾘｵ｡
ｵｽﾊﾟｰ｡
We’ll just have to risk
getting in close to finish it!
一か八か 懐に飛び込んで決める｡
Riolu, use Force Palm!
ﾘｵﾙ はっけいだ！
No! Don’t fight up close!
いかん 接近戦は！
Watch out, Riolu!
ﾘｵﾙ 危ない！
ｵｽﾊﾟｰ｡
ｸｯ どうすりゃいい？
What can we do?
We can’t get close unless
we deal with those arms.
あの腕をなんとかしなきゃ
近づけない｡
ﾊｧ ﾊｧ…｡
Satoshi seems to be
having a tough time.
やりにくそうだ ｻﾄｼ｡
今のは ｵﾄｽﾊﾟｽが誘ったんだ｡
Otosupus lured them into that.
All right, Riolu,
here’s what we’ll do.
よし｡ この手でいくぞ ﾘｵﾙ｡
Strike under its feet!
Force Palm!
足元へたたきつけろ｡ はっけい！
ﾘｵ！
なんと！
きた！ ｻﾄｼのﾑﾁｬｸﾁｬ｡
Oh, my!
Here comes Satoshi’s crazy antics!
Now!
Use another Force Palm!
今だ｡ もう一度 はっけい！
Riolu!
ﾘｵﾙ！
たこがため！
Octolock!
ｵｽﾊﾟ！
Octolock?!
たこがため!?
ﾋﾟｶ！
His crazy antics didn’t work?!
ﾑﾁｬｸﾁｬが効かない!?
ﾘｵ ﾘｵ…｡
これって寝技？
かかってしまったか｡
Is this ground fighting?
He walked right into her trap.
Riolu, hang in there!
Break free
with Vacuum Wave!
Your technique has too many
wasted movements.
Riolu, your feet!
Kick the floor!
All right!
Great work!
Hang in there, Riolu!
Aqua Break!
Use Reversal!
It knew Reversal?!
A fateful strike that deals more damage
the more damage has been inflicted on the user!
Use Octolock again!
Riolu!
Not good!
Forfeit. Otherwise,
I will bring you down.
We won’t lose!
We made it out before!
ﾘｵﾙ しっかりするんだ｡
脱出だ｡ しんくうは！
Hang in there, Riolu!
ﾘ～ｵ～｡
You leave me no choice.
戦法に無駄が多いです｡
ｸｯ｡
Aqua Break!
ﾋﾟｶﾁｭｰ！
ﾘｵﾙ 足で 足で床をたたくんだ！
Riolu!
ｵｽﾊﾟｰ！
Riolu is unable to battle!
As such, the winner is
Contestant Saito!
ﾋﾟｶﾁｭｰ！
いいぞ！
よし！
I thank you.
Are you okay?!
ﾊｧ ﾊｧ…｡
ﾘｵﾙ 頑張ってくれ！
Based on the results of this battle,
the Pokémon World Championships
rankings will be updated!
ﾊｧ ﾊｧ… ﾘｵ！
ｵｽﾊﾟｰ｡
ｱｸｱﾌﾞﾚｲｸ！
Miss Saito won with ease.
Neither Satoshi’s special crazy antics
nor his attempts to outspeed her did him any good.
きしかいせいだ！
ﾘｵ～ｯ！
Luchabull and Otosupus
are both practically unharmed.
きしかいせいを覚えていたか｡
自分の体力が少ないほど
大きなﾀﾞﾒｰｼﾞを与える運命の一撃｡
I lost...
completely and utterly.
ﾘｵｯ！
She was really tough, huh, Satoshi?
Return, Otosupus.
ｵｽﾊﾟｰ！
もう一度 たこがため！
I take my leave.
Thank you for allowing us
to battle here.
ｵｽﾊﾟｰ！
ﾀｺ！
ﾘｵ！
ﾘｵﾙ！
ﾋﾟｶ！
All right, Go...
Now it’s our turn!
ｵｽﾊﾟｰ｡
ﾘｵ…｡
Who will become your partner?
いかん！
Defeat me,
and the choice is yours!
ｷﾞﾌﾞｱｯﾌﾟしなさい｡ さもなければ
このまま落とします｡
Right now?!
俺たちは負けない｡
さっきだって脱出できたんだ｡
ﾘｵﾙ 頑張れ！
ﾘｵｰｯ｡
しかたないですね｡ ｱｸｱﾌﾞﾚｲｸ｡
I guess you were
the only winner today.
I got Ebiwarar!
Riolu. Kamonegi.
Sorry. You guys practiced so hard,
but I still lost.
ﾘｵﾙ！
I’ve never had a battle
like that before.
But that won’t happen again!
ﾘｵﾙ 戦闘不能｡
I’ll get my revenge on Miss Saito,
sooner or later!
よって勝者 ｻｲﾄｳ選手｡
The Gym Leader Saito...
ありがとうございました｡
...has given Satoshi his first taste of defeat
in the Championships.
He still has a long way to go
to reach the Monarch, Dande!
大丈夫か？
ﾋﾟｶ！
今回のﾊﾞﾄﾙをもとに
ﾎﾟｹﾓﾝ･ﾜｰﾙﾄﾞ･ﾁｬﾝﾋﾟｵﾝｼｯﾌﾟｽ[外:583134B86E7D90960F64C5B863196978]
i
r
o
t
i
r
h
S
n
o
m
é
k
o
P
i
r
o
t
i
r
h
S
n
o
m
é
k
o
P
i
r
o
t
i
r
h
S
n
o
m
é
k
o
P
i
r
o
t
i
r
h
S
n
o
m
é
k
o
P
i
r
o
t
i
r
h
S
n
o
m
é
k
o
P
Let’s play Pokémon Shiritori!
ﾗﾝｷﾝｸﾞの変動を行います｡
(Mew → Zamazenta Ver.)
ﾋﾞﾌ…｡
ｻｲﾄｳさんの圧勝だった｡
Mew!
(Mew → Zamazenta Ver.)
Pokémon Shiritori
Warrgle!
RU
OOGU
U
MIYU
Runpappa!
PA
NPAP
RU
SU
RUGAMO
U
Pawou!
UWA
PA
ｻﾄｼの得意のﾑﾁｬｸﾁｬもｽﾋﾟｰﾄﾞ勝負も
まるで通用しなかった｡
Strike!
KU
TORAI
SU
Ulgamoth!
Cresselia!
A
RESERI
KU
Amakaji!
JI
MAKA
A
Chobomaki!
KI
YOBOMA
CHI
Jirachi!
RAA
JI
Kibago!
GO
BA
KI
ﾙﾁｬﾌﾞﾙもｵﾄｽﾊﾟｽも ほぼ無傷｡
Gonbe!
BE
N
GO
A
ZA
RII
FU
Bayleaf!
IRII
BE
Freezer!
Zacian!
N
SHIA
ZA
俺の… 完敗だ｡
Shiritori set to Pokémon Techno
Chain the names of Pokémon
ﾋﾟｶﾁｭ…｡
Even if it ends in an “N”, I still love it
やりにくい相手だったな ｻﾄｼ｡
Okay, let’s go one more time!
ｵﾄｽﾊﾟｽ 戻ってください｡
Mew!
A
PA
​
U
Wooper!
MIYU
SU
CHIRI
PA
Pachirisu!
Absol!
A
NABA
SU
Sunaba!
RA
NAAA
RU
Lunala!
BUSO
A
TO
BIFUT
RA
Rabbifoot!
では 私はこれで｡
SU
ROPIU
TO
Tropius!
BA
BURAA
BI
Vibrava!
NAHE
SU
Sunahebi!
この場を貸していただき
ありがとうございました｡
Burshamo!
MO
SHAA
O
RO
KU
MO
Mokuroh!
Mooland!
DO
URAN
MU
TO
RO
Rotom!
O
ODORI
DO
Dodorio!
SU
TOSUPA
O
Otosupus!
NA
WAN
SU
Swanna!
A
DA
MEHA
SA
Samehada!
ZONOKU
NA
Nazonokusa!
Darkrai!
I
AKURA
DA
Iwanko!
KO
WAN
I
PI
KORU
SU
Scorupi!
OTA
KO
Cortoise!
Pippi!
PI
P
ﾋﾟｶ…｡
Pinpuku!
KU
NPU
PI
Mankey!
I
KI
N
MA
Kunugidama!
NUGIDA
KU
RI
MO
KI
Kimori!
Ligray!
E
RE
GU
Rayquaza!
ZA
KKUU
RE
Zamazenta!
TA
MAZEN
ZA
Shiritori with the Music Club
さて ｺﾞｳくん 次は我々の番だ｡
Chain the names of Pokémon
へっ？
誰が君の仲間となるか[外:583134B86E7D90960F64C5B863196978]
Learn lots of Pokémon names
わしに勝てば選び放題だ｡
All right! Now you’re set for success!
今からですか？
ﾋﾞﾌ！
Let’s play Pokémon Shiritori!
i
r
o
t
i
r
h
S
n
o
m
é
k
o
P
i
r
o
t
i
r
h
S
n
o
m
é
k
o
P
i
r
o
t
i
r
h
S
n
o
m
é
k
o
P
i
r
o
t
i
r
h
S
n
o
m
é
k
o
P
i
r
o
t
i
r
h
S
n
o
m
é
k
o
P
(Mew → Zamazenta Ver.)
ﾘｵ！
ｶﾓ｡
うん｡
今日 うまくいったのはｺﾞｳだけか｡
Now! Onto the next adventure!
ｴﾋﾞﾜﾗｰ ｹﾞｯﾄだぜ｡
ｴﾋﾞｴﾋﾞ ｴﾋﾞ！
Go!
I’ve decided! I’ll get Pikachu!
ﾘｵﾙ ｶﾓﾈｷﾞ せっかくここまで
練習をしてきたのに[外:583134B86E7D90960F64C5B863196978]
What brought this on?
I gotta do this
if I’m gonna get every Pokémon, yeah?
負けちゃって ごめんな｡
ﾘｵ～｡
Well, I guess...
ｶﾓ～｡
Satoshi, look!
A Thunder Stone?!
ﾋﾟｶﾁｭｰ｡
あんなﾊﾞﾄﾙは初めてだった｡
What?! Satoshi’s Pikachu is evolving?!
だけど次は こうはいかない｡
Next time, on Pocket Monsters:
いつかｻｲﾄｳさんにﾘﾍﾞﾝｼﾞしてみせる｡
I'll Get Pikachu!!
I’ll Get Pikachu!!
＜ｼﾞﾑﾘｰﾀﾞｰ ｻｲﾄｳによって[外:583134B86E7D90960F64C5B863196978]
ﾁｬﾝﾋﾟｵﾝｼｯﾌﾟｽ初の
敗北を味わったｻﾄｼ｡
王者ﾀﾞﾝﾃﾞまでの道のりは
まだまだ遠い＞
これまでに密着した
2,000人を超える警察官たち｡
そのなかから難事件を
見事 解決に導いた[外:583134B86E7D90960F64C5B863196978]
ｽｺﾞ腕お巡りさんの活躍を厳選｡
まずは 驚異の記憶力で
ひき逃げ犯を追い詰めた[外:583134B86E7D90960F64C5B863196978]
埼玉県警
横山巡査部長の事件簿｡